kimptonhotels.com 2012-09-18

# Kimpton Hotels & Restaurants - Privacy Statement

| 

###### Privacy

Kimpton Hotel & Restaurant Group uses your personal information in order to fulfill our commitment to providing an unparalleled guest service experience. As part of that undertaking, we are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the personal information that we gather.

As one of our guests, you understand and agree that we collect, use and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy for Guests (this " **Policy** ").

The term "personal information" in this Policy refers to information which does or is capable of identifying you as an individual. The types of personal information that we process (which may vary by jurisdiction based on applicable law) include:

  * your name, gender, home and work contact details, business title, date and place of birth, nationality and passport and visa information;
  * guest stay information, including the hotels where you have stayed, date of arrival and departure, goods and services purchased, special requests made, observations about your service preferences (including room and holiday preferences), telephone numbers dialed and faxes and telephone messages received;
  * your credit card details, Kimpton inTouch frequent guest program member information, online user account details, profile or password details and any frequent flyer or travel partner program affiliation;
  * any information necessary to fulfill special requests (e.g., health conditions that require specific accommodation, purchase of goods and services);
  * information you provide regarding your marketing preferences or in the course of participating in surveys, contests or promotional offers;
  * information collected through the use of closed circuit television systems, card key and other security systems; and
  * contact and other relevant details concerning the employees of corporate accounts and vendors and other individuals with whom we do business (e.g., travel agents or meeting and event planners).

Most of the personal information we process is information that you or someone acting on your behalf knowingly provides to us. However, in some instances, we process personal information that we are able to infer about you based on other information you provide to us or on our interactions with you, or personal information about you that we receive from a third party.

Demographic and profile data is collected at our site, and we use this data in two main ways:

First, we analyze visitor information in aggregate, which means that we collect information about thousands of site visits and analyze it as a whole. This kind of study involves looking for trends among many visitors to our site, rather than analyzing information about any individual visitor. Examples include researching which parts of the site are accessed most frequently or determining which products are most attractive to our users.

Second, we may use specific information you provide to help us customize our communications with you and improve our service to you when you visit any Kimpton property, to conduct market research, customer satisfaction and quality assurance surveys and to direct marketing and sales promotions. For instance, if you inform us of a room or service preference, we will attempt to satisfy that request when you visit us in the future and may send you promotions relating to that preference.

We use third parties to build and manage these communication and preference systems, and our arrangements with these third parties prohibit them from disclosing your personal information.

Specifically, subject to applicable laws, we may collect, use and disclose relevant portions of your personal information in order to:

  * provide and charge for the hotel accommodation and other goods and services you purchase;
  * provide you with a better, more personalized level of service;
  * administer the Kimpton inTouch frequent guest program;
  * fulfill contractual obligations to you, anyone involved in the process of making your travel arrangements (e.g., travel agents, group travel organizers or your employer) and vendors (e.g., credit card companies, airline operators and other loyalty programs);
  * conduct market research,customer satisfaction and quality assurance surveys, direct marketing and sales promotions;
  * respond to requests for information and services;
  * provide for the safety and security of staff, guests and other visitors;
  * administer general record keeping; and
  * meet legal and regulatory requirements

We reveal Personally Identifiable Information about you to unaffiliated third parties if:

  * you request or authorize it;
  * the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you;
  * the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.);
  * the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets);
  * the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or
  * to others as described in this Privacy Policy.

Every e-mail communication from Kimpton or its authorized agents, excepting reservation confirmations and the like, will contain clear and obvious instructions for how you can remove yourself from that mailing list ("Opt-out"). You may also unsubscribe at any time by completing our subscription preferences form at  
<http://kimptongroup.ip02.com/kimptongroup/prefs>.

Third party Internet sites available through advertising and other links on our site have separate privacy and data collection practices. If you click on a link found on our websites or on any other website, you should always look at the location bar within your browser to determine whether you have been linked to a different website. This Policy, and our responsibility, is limited to our own information collection practices. We are not responsible for, and cannot always ensure, the information collection practices or privacy policies of other websites maintained by third parties or our service providers where you submit your personal information directly to such websites. In addition, we cannot ensure the content of the websites maintained by these third parties or our service providers, even if accessible using a link from our websites. We urge you to read the privacy and security policies of any external sites before providing any personal information while accessing those sites.

We work diligently to protect the security of your personal information, including credit card information, during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Your data is kept in a highly secure environment protected from access by unauthorized parties. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your customer profile by ensuring that you logoff when you have finished visiting our site.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you visit our site. We use cookies to improve your experience, for instance, by allowing you to login without typing the registered email address or registration number and password. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major sites.

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness.

We use WebTrends Reporting Service to analyze traffic to our web site. WebTrends Reporting Service does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services, WebTrends Reporting Service does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Reporting Service only collects aggregate data. You are welcome to refer to the WebTrends Reporting Service Privacy Policy to learn how they collect and use information. You can find the WebTrends Reporting Service Privacy Policy here: <http://ondemand.webtrends.com/privacypolicy.asp>

We may employ a browser monitor within web pages on our site in order to determine your browser status and the client-side metrics relating to page loading. We constantly seek ways to improve page load times for our visitors and may ultimately use these metrics for such purposes. Any such browser monitor will only be active while the user is active on our site. For your protection, any such browser monitor will not require an executable (*.exe) application.

Like most Internet sites, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

Our websites do not sell products or services for purchase by children. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use our websites with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Just as our business changes constantly, this Policy may also change. To assist you, this Policy has an effective date set out at the end of this document.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies or any other matter, please contact us at  
[privacypolicy@kimptongroup.com](mailto:privacypolicy@kimptongroup.com).

_Effective Date: **March 25, 2011**_

|
